"Only for love"
“只为爱”
Part (3)
第(3)部分
(The reporter has arrived for the introduction of Director Xi Sangyu )
（记者已到现场听取奚桑榆主任介绍 ）
Isn't it one o'clock in the afternoon?
现在不是下午一点吗？
(He arrived early, so I'll make him wait)
（他来得早， 我就让他等一下）
No need, ask him to come in
不用了，请他进来吧
Hello, Director Xi
习主任您好
you..
你..
My name is Xu Yuling, a reporter from Financial Introduction
我是财经导报记者徐玉玲
My colleague can't come today because he has some business
我的同事 今天有事不能来
So I was transferred to do this interview
所以我 被调去做这次采访
Thank you
谢谢
So let's get started, director
那么我们开始吧，导演
Wait a minute, reporter gold
等一下，金记者
Can I see your draft?
我可以看看你的草稿吗？
Got it
知道了
(Draft interview for Xian)
（西安采访稿）
So let's get started
让我们开始吧
Min Yu Yun Chum is a subsidiary company of Min Yu Group
闽宇云春是 闽宇集团的子公司
From the most influential appraisal firm in the field
来自该领域最具影响力的评估公司
He is rated AA
他的评级是AA
Because of his promising vision
因为他的远见卓识
It even raised the parent company's reliability standards
它甚至提高了母公司的可靠性标准
Yun Chum's future is really promising
Yun Chum的未来真是 可期
The main speaker of this interview is Min Yu Yunchum
本次采访的主讲人为 Min Yu Yunchum
Development plan and necessary preparation for the next five years
未来五年发展规划及必要准备
including his role under the parent company
包括他在母公司的角色
Other related questions
其他相关问题
First I want to ask
首先我想问
The director's point of view when he founded Min Yu Yun Chum
创办Min Yu Yun Chum时董事的观点
Subscribe to this
订阅此
Hello
你好
Hello, I'm a financial reporter
大家好，我是财经 记者
Register first
先注册
Are all the reporters at your magazine beautiful like you?
你们杂志社的记者都是 像你一样漂亮吗？
(Xu Yu Lin)
(Xu Yu Lin)
(Why is Xu Yuling's name in the guest log ?)
（为什么嘉宾日志里有徐玉玲的名字？）
Thank you
谢谢
Secretary Chan
陈秘书
About the reporter
关于记者
Interview with director Xi scheduled for an hour today
今天安排一个小时采访习主席
Did it go according to plan?
事情按计划进行吗？
You have an issue, don't you?
你有问题，不是吗？
Your colleague has already done the interview for you
你的同事 已经帮你面试完了
He came at lunchtime, which is when Director Xi is busy
他是午饭时间来的， 正是习主任忙碌的时候
He also said that you gave him away
他还说你把他出卖了
Sorry , there was a disconnection in our group
抱歉，我们的群组断线了
I'm tired of coming this far
我厌倦了这么远
I'm not tired
我不累
But..
但..
I have an appointment with the director Xi My Shin this afternoon
今天下午我和席美信导演有个约会
Director Xi has to go outside, so I will return to the reporter
习主任要出去了， 我这就回去找记者
The interview is over today
今天面试结束了
I have been waiting for this interview for a long time
我等待这次采访已经很久了
I got the chance today
我今天有机会
Is it okay now?
现在可以了吗？
Director Xi has moderated the basic part of the interview
习主任主持了采访的基本部分
But five questions about Yun Chum's future
但关于 Yun Chum 未来的五个问题
You still haven't answered
你还没回答
It will only take a little time
只需要一点时间
May I
我可以
What are those five questions?
这五个问题是什么？
Question 1 : As a subsidiary company of Min Yu Group
问题一：作为闽宇集团的子公司
Operated independently from the parent company
独立于母公司运营
Do you have plans to expand into larger markets?
您有计划扩展到更大的市场吗？
Question 2: Regarding the cooperation between Kuen Group and Yun Chum
问题二：关于坤集团与Yun Chum的合作
Besides looking to invest in more innovative areas
除了寻求投资更多创新领域
Any other long-term plans?
还有其他长期计划吗？
Question 3 : Is it your plan to return to China for Professor Yuyo ?
问题3：您有计划让Yuyo教授回国吗？
This is your first personal interview
这是您的第一次个人采访
It is the first step towards understanding Yun Chum's exterior
这是了解Yun Chum外表的第一步
So..
所以..
i believe
我相信
The media and the public
媒体和公众
Won't you allow me to understand Yun Chum more deeply?
你就不能让我更深入地了解Yun Chum吗？
followed
已关注
Director Xi
奚主任
Can I ask, we are going now..
请问一下，我们现在就去..
(Ask my uncle to pick up the phone)
（请叔叔接电话）
(Little God?)
（小神？）
I told him that if he doesn't listen, don't come in front of me again
我告诉他，如果他不听的话， 就不要再出现在我面前
You heard what Director Xi said
习主席说的你都听到了
(Very influential)
（影响很大）
(If it is so influential)
（如果影响力这么大的话）
(Why don't you teach yourself not to be a mistress)
（你为什么不教自己 不要当小三）
Director Xi
奚主任
Driver Fan is waiting in a commercial vehicle
范司机 在商务车内等候
Ask him to come
请他来
The reporter might want to sit in this car
记者 可能想坐这辆车
Am I?
我是吗？
They said in the car that I have to drive for two hours
他们在车上说我要开两个小时
Didn't you say you could use the time in the car earlier ?
你不是说可以早点利用车上的时间吗？
Of course, no problem
当然没问题
(You can also say under the car)
（也可以说在车下）
Director Xi
奚主任
( I don't think I should interview Shi Xian in this way )
（我觉得我不应该以这种方式采访石贤）
(trust me)
（相信我）
(Xiang is a man too)
（翔也是 男人）
(A man cannot refuse such an approach )
（男人无法拒绝这样的做法）
(Isn't the Shanshan method useless?)
（杉杉的方法是不是没什么用了？）
Is it cold?
天冷吗？
It's not cold
天气不冷
Put down the torch
放下火把
Well done, Director Xi
习主任干得好
(Just saying I'm not cold doesn't mean I'm hot)
（只是说我不冷 并不意味着我很热）
My time is limited
我的时间有限
Director Xi Before we officially start
习主任在正式开始之前
Let's talk about the other first , so it's easy
先说说其他的吧 ，这样就很简单了
What do you want to say?
你想说什么？
Director Xi will certainly rarely accept an interview
习主席肯定 很少接受采访
Usually, before we start the interview, we get to know the interviewee a little bit
通常，在开始采访之前， 我们会稍微了解一下受访者
So let's introduce ourselves
那么让我们自我介绍一下
We should get to know each other a little
我们应该稍微了解一下彼此
I am a reporter from Keng Shuyi's financial introduction
我是记者铿淑仪 财经介绍
I am really honored to interview Director Xi today
今天非常荣幸采访习主席
Shi Xiang, 27, is the CEO of Min Yu Yun Chum
Shi Xiang, 27, is the CEO of Min Yu Yun Chum
(Why do I think of such a bad method ?)
（为什么我会想到这么糟糕的方法？）
Director Xi is really young and promising
习主任真是 年轻有为
(I just said this)
（我只是说这个）
In fact, I was waiting for you at Wanara Farm the first time
其实我第一次就在瓦纳拉农场等你
I was really lucky
我真的很幸运
I heard that director Shao Kuon of the Kuon group will also be there
听说 Kuon集团的导演Shao Kuon也会到场
Because you and he are close
因为你和他很亲近
Enough to encourage
足以鼓励
Although he said that he rarely attends such events
虽然他说自己很少参加这样的活动
I can't tell if fate favors me
我不知道命运是否 眷顾我
Anyway, for our journalists, publication day is a holiday
无论如何，对于我们记者来说， 出版日就是一个假期
Unfortunately, I was really lucky
不幸的是，我真的很幸运
I didn't get the chance to interview you, but I got the chance to meet you
我没有机会采访你，但 我有机会见到你
So, the cooperation between Shin and the Ku group
那么，Shin和Ku集团的合作
Will it be officially announced soon?
很快就会正式宣布吗？
Are you going to expand into areas of mutual interest ?
你们打算扩展到共同感兴趣的领域吗？
Director Xi, what did I say wrong?
习主任，我说错什么了吗？
Why do you think Kum Group wants to join Yun Chum?
您认为 Kum Group 为什么 要加入 Yun Chum？
What do you think Yun Chum and Kum Group will do?
您认为 Yun Chum 和 Kum 集团会做什么？
Have you finished asking?
你问完了吗？
Director Xi, I have one more question
习主任，我还有一个问题
Why didn't you stay at Min Yu Group at that time?
当时为什么不留在民宇集团？
Did you choose to start your own business?
您选择自己创业吗？
Did your father support your decision?
你的父亲支持你的决定吗？
I am getting old
我渐渐老了
I can't handle many things anymore
我无法再处理很多事情
This time, Min Yu was able to survive thanks to some old friends
这次，珉宇能活下来， 多亏了一些老朋友
Min Yu's future
Min Yu's future
It depends on you
这取决于你
In fact, my husband is more suitable than me
其实我老公 比我更适合
But your lineage is Xi
但你的血统是习
Yu Yu needs you
于宇需要你
Her husband is a member of the Xi family
她的丈夫是习氏家族的成员
I still want to do something meaningful and happy for myself
我还是想做一些 对自己有意义、快乐的事情
How do you..
你怎么..
Have you thought it through?
你想清楚了吗？
I have thought it through
我已经想清楚了
This road..
这条路..
It will be very difficult
这将是非常困难的
I know
我知道
But someone has to step up
但必须有人 挺身而出
You..
你..
I will be retiring soon
我很快就要退休了
The house is the car
房子就是车
You will not need to use the latter
您不需要使用后者
You take it
你拿着吧
Thank you, father
谢谢你，父亲
Two hours have passed
两个小时过去了
You can return now
您现在可以返回
( How do you get back from such a remote place ?)
（这么偏僻的地方怎么回来？）
(Do you have to ride a horse?)
（一定要骑马吗？）
(Shi Xian is very angry)
（世贤很生气）
( I want you to give up in this remote place )
（我要你在这个偏僻的地方放弃）
(absolutely impossible)
（绝对不可能）
(I came by this car and must return with this car)
（我是乘这辆车来的 ，也必须乘这辆车回来）
Director Xi Sing's voice is very good to listen to
席声导演的声音 很好听
Through some of your answers
通过你的一些回答
Can we use it as an audio file in our digital magazine ?
我们可以将其用作数字杂志中的音频文件吗？
I want to have my full view
我想要看到我的全貌
So it means that I got it
所以这意味着我明白了
Wait a minute, Director Xi
习主任等一下
I have one last question
我还有最后一个问题
say
说
Do you have a girlfriend?
你有女朋友吗？
This question is to satisfy the curiosity of our readers
这个问题是 为了满足读者的好奇心
It doesn't matter if Director Xi doesn't want to answer
习主任不想回答也没关系
Actually, my last question
事实上，我的最后一个问题
A young investment company like Min Yu Yun Chum
像 Min Yu Yun Chum 这样的年轻投资公司
Why did you decide to invest in Le Ann technology ?
为什么决定投资乐安科技？
Because the long-term research and development chain will not be immediately profitable
因为长期的研发链 不会立即盈利
Aren't you worried?
你不担心吗？
Is this question just to satisfy readers' curiosity?
这个问题 只是为了满足读者的好奇心吗？
As a financial reporter
作为一名财经记者
After researching various sources of information
在研究了各种信息来源后
A scholarly review
学术评论
Xian
西安
This is it
就是这个
Teacher Kun
坤老师
Hello, I'm Kung Shuyi, a reporter from Financial Introduction
大家好，我是财经导报记者孔淑仪
Do you know me?
你知道我吗？
In university, I majored in journalism but minored in finance
大学时，我主修新闻学， 辅修金融
During the first class of the finance lesson, the teacher talked about my uncle
金融课第一节课时， 老师谈到了我的叔叔
And I work with my uncle every day
我每天都和叔叔一起工作
On the walls of our office
在我们办公室的墙上
There is a magazine cover picture of uncle and teacher Shi Wan Kuon
里面有石万坤叔叔和老师的杂志封面图
So, my uncle's name has been with me throughout my university life
所以，叔叔的名字 伴随了我整个大学生活
My uncle's existence is a companion in my daily work life
叔叔的存在是 我日常工作生活中的陪伴
Even though he doesn't appear in public much now, everyone knows him
虽然现在很少出现在公众面前，但是 大家都认识他
Uncle's reputation is unshakable like Titaung
叔叔的名声 就像Titaung一样不可动摇
I just said, what is your name?
我刚刚说，你叫什么名字？
Keng Shuyi, right?
Keng Shuyi, right?
Yes
是的
Keng Shuyi
Keng Shuyi
I remember you
我记得你
I have read three or four of your articles
我读过你的三四篇文章
Not bad writing
写得还不错
It is serious and has a position
是认真的，有立场的
Unexpectedly, when I met her in person, she was a little girl
没想到当我见到她本人时， 她还是一个小女孩
Too much praise
太多的赞美
I think I came to you alone again
我想我又独自来到你身边
I didn't prepare anything
我什么都没准备
Girl, don't blame me for that
女孩， 别怪我
This guy has never brought any girl here
这家伙从来没有带过任何女孩来这里
- Uncle Le Ku, in fact, he is.. - My God..
- 乐库叔叔，其实他是.. - 天啊..
This place is very beautiful
这个地方非常美丽
These horses are also very beautiful
这些马也很漂亮
I heard that my uncle's greatest hobby is horse riding
听说叔叔 最大的爱好是骑马
There will be quite a few horses
会有不少马
This is not my best horse yet
这还不是我最好的马
The best horses are inside
最好的马都在里面
Is it still there?
还在吗？
Do you want to see?
你想要看？
Followed the Shiyan girl
跟着十堰姑娘
come with me
跟我来
Why?
为什么？
Is there a problem with Director Xi?
习主席有问题吗？
Teacher Kuon invited me
库恩老师邀请我
What is there to fear?
有什么可害怕的呢？
Mixing me with horse feed is not enough to feed the horses
我和马饲料混合 不足以喂马
I'll go in and change my shirt
我进去换件衬衫
I will wait
我将等待
Has Shi Xiang entered?
石翔进来了吗？
How long have you known Xian?
你认识西安多久了？
Not too long ago
不久前
It seems so
看来是这样
Can you ride a horse?
你会骑马吗？
I don't know how to ride
我不知道怎么骑
Inside were some old riding clothes that my wife wore
里面是我妻子穿过的一些旧骑马服
If you don't mind, you can wear it
不介意的话可以穿
You should try it when it arrives
当它到达时你应该尝试一下
you do not say
可不是嘛
This side
这边
My wife's physique is not that different from yours
我老婆的体质 和你没啥区别
Enough with this
受够了这个
Thank you, Mr. Kun
谢谢坤先生
I will wait for you outside
我会在外面等你
I can't hear a sound
我听不到声音
It's enough to leave
离开就够了
Director Xi
奚主任
I don't wear this belt
我不戴这条腰带
Can you teach me?
你可以教我吗？
(You still want to fool me)
（你还想骗我）
If you can't wear it, don't ride it
如果你不能穿，就不要骑
Mark said once
马克曾经说过
If a woman wants to pursue a man
如果一个女人 想追求一个男人
There is no wall that she cannot overcome
没有她不能逾越的墙
There is no fortress she can break down
没有她可以攻破的堡垒
There is no worry he can't shake off
不用担心他无法摆脱
Even a god cannot control him
就算是神也无法控制他
So what am I now facing an impenetrable fortress?
那我现在面对的是什么 坚不可摧的堡垒呢？
Dangerous trip?
危险的旅行？
Wrath of God?
天神的愤怒？
Not one
不是一个
A small rejection
小小的拒绝
You can cross over
你可以穿越
come come
怎样怎样
This horse is the most delicate
这匹马最娇嫩
After that, ask Shi Xian to teach you
之后请石贤教你
come come
怎样怎样
Be careful
当心
A really handsome prince
真的是一个很帅气的王子
So the horse
所以马
Or a princess?
还是公主？
Really clever
真聪明
It looks so delicate to me..
对我来说看起来很精致..
We..
我们..
So, Director Xi, please teach me how to ride a horse
那么习主任， 请教我骑马吧
Go up
上
Lead the director
带领导演
In this way, you will be able to teach horse riding
这样你就可以教骑马了
Relax and learn
放松并学习
Well done
做得好
I 'm a little nervous because it's my first time riding a horse
我有点紧张，因为这是我第一次骑马
Be sure to sit down
一定要坐下来
What
什么
Slowly slowly
慢慢来
Slowly
慢慢地
Why don't you?
你为什么不呢？
No, I..
不，我..
Just get the experience
只是获得经验
It is the most delicate horse in the whole horse race
它是整个赛马场中最娇弱的一匹马
I am also very close to you
我也离你很近
Asking you to teach a girl to ride a horse
请你教一个女孩骑马
Why scare him?
为什么要吓唬他？
He is brave and doesn't get scared easily
他很勇敢， 不容易被吓到
Before, I asked you to rest on the horse slope
之前我叫你 在马坡上休息
I don't come because I have too much work
我不来是因为我有太多工作
Why did you suddenly have time today and bring the girl?
今天怎么突然有时间， 把那个女孩带来了？
Suddenly wanted to come
突然很想来
This girl is quite interesting
这个女孩还蛮有趣的
It's definitely the way you like it
这绝对是你喜欢的方式
is that so
是这样吗
It's not about anything now
现在已经不是什么事情了
Not now, but if it continues, something will happen
现在不是，但如果继续下去， 就会发生一些事情
Did you do such a rough road on purpose?
你是故意走这么崎岖的路吗？
He even mocked me in front of Mr. Ku
他还当着库先生的面嘲笑我
Is it even human?
这还是人类吗？
Mark can't always be right
马克不可能总是对的
At least I couldn't even pass the saddle of the horse in front of me
至少我连眼前的马鞍都过不去
gone
消失了
Yes
是的
A lot of things may be nothing at first
很多事情 一开始可能没什么
But as it goes on, there are many possibilities
但随着事情的发展， 还有很多可能性
You're talking
你在说话
Le Ann technology?
乐安科技？
In all cases
在所有情况下
Yun Chum is the same
云春也是一样
I have heard from Kukyi
我从库基那里听说
I was a little worried about you at first
一开始我有点担心你
But now it looks like I'm too nervous
但现在看来 是我太紧张了
Xian
西安
The path you want to take
你想要走的路
It's long and not easy
很长而且不容易
Min Yu has just passed a mountain and decided to establish Yun Chum
敏宇刚刚翻过一座山， 决定成立Yun Chum
Longtian and others helped Min Yu survive
龙天等人 帮助敏宇活了下来
Now help you too
现在也帮助你
You must remember this grace
你一定要记住这份恩典
Yun Chum wants stability more than anything else at this stage
Yun Chum 现阶段最需要的是稳定
You don't need to make Luang Thanh and other people angry
你不需要让Luang Thanh和其他人 生气
If they're not happy, you're going to have a hard time
如果他们不高兴，你就会过得很艰难
I remember
我记得
So I have to do better
所以我必须做得更好
As long as the decisions are right, all dissatisfaction will be temporary
只要决定是对的， 一切不满都是暂时的
I also heard about Leyin's case
我也听说了乐音的事
It's a good choice to invest in them to some extent
在某种程度上投资它们是一个不错的选择
As soon as the funds came from Kuon Group
库恩集团的资金一到
Yun Chum can invest in both companies
Yun Chum 可以投资两家公司
No need to create unnecessary tension
无需制造不必要的紧张
They are all your father's old friends
他们都是你父亲的老朋友
No need to embarrass them
没必要让他们难堪
Uncle, I understand what Uncle wants to say
叔叔， 我明白叔叔想说什么
But Yun Chum is still very young
但Yun Chum还很年轻
I want him to be pure and good at one thing
我希望他纯洁并 擅长一件事
We don't want to change our philosophy and purpose to please others
我们不想为了取悦他人而改变我们的理念和宗旨
Because of Min Yu's crisis
因为敏宇的危机
I understood
我明白了
A modern company needs more professional and refined management
现代企业需要更加专业化、 精细化的管理
Have you come back to avoid it?
你回来躲避了吗？
What are you doing now?
你在干什么？
It has been three or four days since I returned
回来已经三四天了
I'm wasting my life doing nothing
我浪费生命无所事事
I plan to get him a job to gain experience
我打算给他找份工作来积累经验
You just said it yourself
你刚才自己也说了
Sometimes some people may be nothing at first, right?
有时候有些人一开始可能什么都不是，对吧？
But as it goes on, there are many possibilities
但随着事情的发展， 还有很多可能性
Xiao Yue is a smart child
小月是个聪明的孩子
If you train well, you can become very good
如果你训练得好， 你可以变得非常优秀
It is possible
有可能的
I just don't know how to trigger those possibilities
我只是不知道如何触发这些可能性
Or ask him to join a group of dicks
或者叫他加入一群混蛋
To force him to work at the barn?
强迫他去谷仓干活？
So I don't know who should work for whom
所以 我不知道谁应该为谁工作
Uncle didn't know that Ku Kyi always wanted him
叔叔不知道 古吉一直想要他
That's right
这是正确的
If you really want to train him
如果你真的想训练他
He has to go to a completely unfamiliar environment
他必须去一个完全陌生的环境
This poor boy can neither study nor play sports
这个可怜的男孩既不能学习也不能 运动
What company would want him?
哪个公司要他？
Did Ekanta hire him as a bribe?
Ekanta 雇用他是为了贿赂吗？
Don't tell the child that
不要告诉孩子
Xiao Yue is smart, happy, and emotionally mature
小月聪明、快乐、 情感成熟
I like to talk to people
我喜欢与人交谈
Ask him to be a reporter
请他当记者
Did he study journalism abroad?
他在国外学新闻吗？
Major and work bite
主要和工作咬合
Reporter
记者
A man like him?
像他这样的男人？
So what kind of person do you think a journalist should be?
那么您认为记者 应该成为什么样的人呢？
Xin can win the best actor Oscar in China
辛 能获得中国奥斯卡最佳男主角
This is the form
这是表格
It was as if he had just done such an act
就好像他刚刚做了这样的举动一样
I think I might have to give it a try
我想我可能得尝试一下
I had to try it
我不得不尝试一下
I have a journalist friend who can help
我有一位记者朋友 可以提供帮助
Do you also know the reporters of U Le Koon ?
你也认识U Le Koon的记者吗？
The reporters know me
记者认识我
Still watching
仍在观看
You want to see my shame
你想看我的耻辱
Let's see
让我们来看看
You don't have much chance anymore
你已经没有多少机会了
Don't think about seeing me again
不要再想再见到我
Chan Shanro
Chan Shanro
Director Xi
奚主任
Secretary Chan said there was an important matter at the company
陈秘书 表示公司有重要事情
Send the reporter back first
先把记者送回去
all right
好的
(Isn't this man hungry?)
（这人不饿吗？）
(Interviewing for two hours , riding a horse for an entire evening)
（采访两个小时 ，骑马一晚上）
(If you forget to eat it on its own, keep it)
（如果忘记单独吃的话，就留着吧）
(How do you not know a little about society?)
（你怎么对社会不了解一点？）
(He doesn't want to throw me a meal, so I'll buy it for him.)
（他不想请我吃饭，所以 我就买给他。）
(but the way he works)
（但他的工作方式）
(quite attractive)
（相当吸引人）
I'm sorry, Director Shiro
对不起，四郎导演
I have to go because there is a matter with Director Xi
我得走了，因为习主任有事
Long Phang, I will go first
龙鹏， 我先走了
You send him home
你送他回家
When he wakes up, see what else he needs
等他醒了，看看他还需要什么
Send it home
寄回家
Well done, Director Xi
习主任干得好
I don't need it anymore, thanks
我不再需要它了，谢谢
(What a strange friendship)
（多么奇怪的友谊啊）
(When I think about it, I don't get impatient)
（想到这里， 我就不再不耐烦了）
(He gave me a car and ran away. How big is that?)
（他给了我一辆车就跑了， 有多大？）
How did you fall asleep in the interviewer's car?
你是怎么在面试官的车里睡着的？
The interviewer is Shi Xian
面试官是石贤
It never happened before
以前从未发生过
Very unprofessional
非常不专业
I fell asleep so soundly
我睡得那么香
I don't know if I have done something shameful yet
我不知道我是否做了什么见不得人的事
On the threshold
在门槛上
The earring is only 25 yuan per side
耳环单面只要25元
Leave it as a gift for teaching me
留下它作为教导我的礼物
Director Xi
奚主任
Thank you very much for coming to see me this time
非常感谢你这次来看我
sit down
坐下
But
但
Some things I really can't control
有些事情我真的无法控制
Anyway, I'm not the only one
无论如何， 我不是唯一一个
I can't just think about my dreams
我不能只考虑我的梦想
I understand
我明白
Yun Chum can give you what Lei Ying can give you
云初能给你的，雷英能给你的
You should also understand
你也应该明白
Yun Chum only because of his sincerity towards Le Ann
云初 只因对乐安的真心
Le Yin offered Le An a fifty million purchase price
乐音向乐安提出五千万收购价
I understand, but
我明白，但是
Fifty million is quite attractive to Le Ann at the moment
五千万 对于目前的乐安来说还是蛮有吸引力的
Director Chen, you also know that Leying still needs investment from us
陈主任，您也知道乐影 还需要我们投资
Not to mention they don't have enough funds for this purchase
更不用说他们 没有足够的资金来进行这次购买
If you look at the long term
如果你着眼长远
Your team should not be at the helm of a combined company at this stage
在此阶段，您的团队 不应掌管合并后的公司
Yun Chum wants to establish China Chip with Le An
Yun Chum 欲与乐安成立中国芯
So what is the best fit for Le Ann at this stage?
那么现阶段最适合乐安的是什么？
Certainly financial support is not for sale
当然，财务支持 是非卖品
Director Xi, you know our value
习主任， 您知道我们的价值
But we have been discussing with Yun Chum for some time now
但我们已经和 Yun Chum 讨论了一段时间了
There was no progress in our cooperation
我们的合作没有任何进展
Now our team is in urgent need of funding for the breakthrough
现在我们团队 急需资金突破
My team has no answer
我的团队没有答案
Give me some time and I will quickly work out the details of the collaboration
给我一些时间， 我会尽快制定合作细节
Solve these problems together
一起解决这些问题
(The legs are already black from the horse's saddle )
（从马鞍上看，腿已经黑了）
( I'm tired to death because of an article)
（ 因为一篇文章累死了）
(it's really not easy)
（确实不容易）
(When I go, I will have a massage)
（我去的时候会做按摩）
(I'm not going to finish the article)
（我不会把这篇文章写完）
Not a bad article, I'm tired
这篇文章不错，我累了
I'm not tired, it's very good to write
不累， 写得很好
Why is there more to say?
为什么还要多说呢？
Sister, I have a few ideas
姐姐我有几个想法
In this interview, Xian shared many innovative views
在这次采访中，冼 分享了许多创新观点
It will appeal to most young readers
它将吸引大多数年轻读者
But he is always secretive, so many people want to know about him
但他总是遮遮掩掩，所以 很多人都想了解他
So, I want to add the audio file of Shi Xian to the digital magazine
所以，我想将时贤的音频文件添加到数字杂志中
Shuyi's idea is good
舒怡的主意不错
But upgrading a digital magazine is not an easy task
但升级数字杂志并不是一件容易的事
It needs a lot of manpower and money
需要大量的人力和金钱
Who will release the audio file you just mentioned ?
谁会发布你刚才提到的音频文件？
I understand, sister
我明白了，姐姐
So we have to catch up with the reading habits of our readers
所以我们 必须跟上读者的阅读习惯
You should take the lead
你应该带头
That will increase sales and upgrade the magazine
这将增加销量并 升级杂志
Once the magazine has been upgraded and given a more diverse presentation style
一旦杂志升级并 赋予更多元化的呈现风格
It can improve the reading experience of readers
可以提高读者的阅读体验
Can give an effective response
能够给出有效的回应
That's why they want to pay for our content
这就是为什么他们想为我们的内容付费
Once we get the funding , we can upgrade and redesign the magazine
一旦我们获得资金，我们就可以升级和重新设计杂志。
To produce the audio file
生成音频文件
I learned the basics online
我在网上学习了基础知识
I can do it now
我现在就能做到
You are really persistent
你真的很执着
I will speak to the editor-in-chief first
我先跟主编说
I will try to help you do this one
我会尽力帮助你做这件事
Thank you sister
谢谢妹妹